and there we have it
thank you so much
for listening
the little blurb
on the back of the book says
Antoine descent exuberies The Little
Prince is an endearing tale of equal
appeal to The Young and the grown-ups
it Blends a simple story of an aviator
forced to land in a remote desert and
his meeting a small boy
The Little Prince from another planet
with an allegory of Human Condition
entertaining thought-provoking
and mind triggering in the process
the beautiful illustrations drawn by the
author are as expressive as his simple
language that conveys deeper shades of
philosophy
the stories of interplanetary travels of
The Little Prince are strange lovely
parables
that have rendered this account to
become the most widely read classic of
our time